[
    {
        "questionNo": "Q1.",
        "question": "What does the prefix \"pre-\" mean?",
        "options": [
            "After",
            "Before",
            "Again",
            "Under"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q2.",
        "question": "Which prefix means \"former\" or \"previously\"?",
        "options": [
            "mis-",
            "un-",
            "non-",
            "ex-"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q3.",
        "question": "Which word means to \"write again\"?",
        "options": [
            "Prewrite",
            "Rewrite",
            "Subwrite",
            "Writeful"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q4.",
        "question": "Which word means \"to spell incorrectly\"?",
        "options": [
            "unspell",
            "nonspell",
            "misspell",
            "exspell"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q5.",
        "question": "Fill in the blank: The ______-profit organisation relies on donations to operate. (non / un)",
        "options": [
            "non",
            "un"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q6.",
        "question": "What is the correct prefix to use with \"view\" to mean \"view beforehand\"?",
        "options": [
            "re-",
            "mis-",
            "pre-",
            "none of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q7.",
        "question": "Which word means \"to think again\"?",
        "options": [
            "Prethink",
            "Rethink",
            "Subthink",
            "Thinkful"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q8.",
        "question": "Which word describes something that was not expected?",
        "options": [
            "misexpected",
            "nonexpected",
            "unexpected",
            "exexpected"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q9.",
        "question": "Fill in the blank: After the fight, the ______-manager decided to start his own business. (mis / ex)",
        "options": [
            "mis",
            "ex"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q10.",
        "question": "Which word means \"to hear incorrectly\"?",
        "options": [
            "unhear",
            "nonhear",
            "mishear",
            "exhear"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q11.",
        "question": "The prefix \"pre-\" means \"after.\"",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q12.",
        "question": "Which word means \"to heat before\"?",
        "options": [
            "Reheat",
            "Preheat",
            "Ex-heat",
            "Misheat"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q13.",
        "question": "Which prefix would you use to describe a person who no longer works as a teacher?",
        "options": [
            "mis-",
            "un-",
            "non-",
            "ex-"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q14.",
        "question": "\"Reuse\" means to use again.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q15.",
        "question": "Which prefix would you use to mean \"to do again\"?",
        "options": [
            "pre-",
            "re-",
            "sub-",
            "-ful"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q16.",
        "question": "Which word describes an action that is against the law?",
        "options": [
            "mislawful",
            "unlawful"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q17.",
        "question": "Fill in the blank: The ______-champion was invited to give a motivational speech. (mis / ex)",
        "options": [
            "mis",
            "ex"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q18.",
        "question": "Which word means \"to use something incorrectly\"?",
        "options": [
            "unuse",
            "nonuse",
            "misuse",
            "exuse"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q19.",
        "question": "Fill in the blank: The detective found several ______matched pairs of footprints. (un / mis)",
        "options": [
            "un",
            "mis"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q20.",
        "question": "Fill in the blank: He is a ______- English speaker. (mis / non)",
        "options": [
            "mis",
            "non"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q21.",
        "question": "The politician's ______ethical behaviour led to his resignation. (un / non)",
        "options": [
            "un",
            "non"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q22.",
        "question": "Which word means \"to plan before\"?",
        "options": [
            "Replan",
            "Misplan",
            "Preplan",
            "Pireplan"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q23.",
        "question": "Which word describes the act of stating something incorrectly?",
        "options": [
            "restate",
            "nonstate",
            "misstate",
            "ex-state"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q24.",
        "question": "Which prefix in \"play\" means to play again?",
        "options": [
            "re-",
            "pre-",
            "sub-",
            "-ful"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q25.",
        "question": "Which word means \"to surface again\"?",
        "options": [
            "Presurface",
            "Ex-surface",
            "Unsurface",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    }
]
